http://www.fancygens.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | FancyGens Car Lights
940-210-5313
[email protected]
D2R HID Kit
Get the latest car lighting news,
product releases, helpful articles and more
when you sign up for Fancygens' newsletter.
Subscribe
Last updated: January 20, 2015
fancygens.com ("us", "we", or "our") operates the http://www.fancygens.com/ website.
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our website.
We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the website. By using the website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at http://www.fancygens.com/privacy-policy.html
Information Collection And Use
While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you.
Log Data
We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.
We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our website, to provide the website on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our website is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Data Deletion
When you request us to delete your account for the Service, your data will be permanently deleted from our servers and further access to your account will not be possible. However, aggregate data derived from your Personal Information may remain on our servers or backup media indefinitely. We also reserve the right to use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
International Transfer
Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
Links To Other Sites
Our website may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children's Privacy
Our website does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a Children under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Created with permission from TermsFeed Generator.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Address:
3403 Boggess Street Decatur, TX 76234
Phone:
940-210-5313
E-mail:
[email protected]
Useful Links
LED
HID
Copyright 2020. All Rights Reserved.
Sitemap
